Linked lists -> linked nodes.
                Each node is independent
                To reach last node, traversing through all is necessary.

                Not contiguous in memory.

                Head = reference to first node.
                Tail's reference is null.

                Node: [value, reference_to_next]

                Tail helps with memory saving -> no need to traverse.


Each node is independent, unlike in arrays.
Size of linked list is not predefined, unlike in arrays.
Insertions are very efficient.
Random access - accessing element is more efficient in arrays.
In linked lists you always need to traverse.


Types = {
         Singly linked list: Each node stores value, and reference to next,
         Circular singly linked list: Reference of last node points to the first one,
         Doubly linked list: Each node stores location of previous and next node,
         Circular doubly linked list: Reference to previous and next, also last to first,


